A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Westmoreland Davis, 1911-1922 (bulk 1918-1922)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Westmoreland Davis, 1911-1922 (bulk 1918-1922)
The Library of Virginia
21567a
34.65 cubic feet (77 boxes)
Davis, Westmoreland, Records of Virginia Governor
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 18 May 1939.
Biographical Information
Westmoreland Davis was born
Scope and Content
Executive Papers, 1911-1922 (bulk 1918-1922), of Westmoreland Davis
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. General Correspondence, 1911-1922 (bulk 1918-1922)
Series II. Extraditions and Pardons, 1918-1922
Contents List
- Series 1: General Correspondence, 1918-1922., Extent: 61 boxes (27.45 cu. ft.). (Box 1-61)
  Series I: General Correspondence, 1911-1922 (bulk 1918-1922)
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Accountancy, State Board of, 1914-1921. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Accountant, State, 1918-1921. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Accountants, Virginia Society of Public, 1918. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Actors Fund of America, 1919. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Adjutant General of the Army, 1920-1922. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Adjutant General, Military, 1918-1920. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adjutant General, Military, 1921-1922. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Advertising Council of America, 1918-1919. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Advisory Board on Taxation, 1913-1914. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Board on Taxation, 1915 January-March. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Advistory Board on Taxation, 1915 April-June. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Advistory Board on Taxation, 1915 July-September. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Advistory Board on Taxation, 1915 October-December. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Advistory Board on Taxation, 1915 (n.d.). (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Advistory Board on Taxation, 1916. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Aerial League, 1918. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Agriculture, Board of, 1918-1921. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Agriculture, Commissioner of, 1918-1921. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Alcoholism, 15th International Congress Against, 1920. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Allotments, 1918-1919. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Bar Association, 1919. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - American Child Hygene Association, 1920. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - American Economic Association, 1918. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - American Institute of Criminal Law and Crimonology, 1918-1920. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - American Legion Concention, 1920-1921. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Anatomical Board, State, 1920-1921. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Angelus, 1918. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Annual Congress on Medical Education and Licensure, 1920. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Anti-Saloon League, 1913. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Anti-Saloon League, 1914 January-March. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Anti-Saloon League, 1914 May-August. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Saloon League, 1914 September 1-9. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Anti-Saloon League, 1914 September 10-15. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Anti-Saloon League, 1914 September 16-19. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Anti-Saloon League, 1914 September 20-28. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Anti-Saloon League, 1914 November-December. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Anti-Saloon League, 1915. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Anti-Saloon League, 1916. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Anti-Saloon League, 1919-1920. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Appeal Agents, 1918. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Appointments to be made by Governor, 1918-1920. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Architects, Engineers, and Surveyors, Board for licensing of, 1920 March-August. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Architects, Engineers, and Surveyors, Board for licensing of, 1920 September-1921. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Armenia, 1919. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Artillery, Distribution of, 1920-1921. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Art Commission of Virginia, 1918-1919. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Art Commission of Virginia, 1920-1922. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Atlantic Deeper Waterways, 1914-1919. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Deeper Waterways, 1920-1922. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Attorney General, Opinions, 1918 February-May. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Attorney General, Opinions, 1918 June-November. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Attorney General, Opinions, 1919. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Attorney General, Opinions, 1920. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Attorney General, Opinions, 1921-1922. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Auditing Committee, 1920. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1918-1921. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Automatic sealing vault, 1919. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Automobile licences, blank applications and law pamphlets, ca. 1916-1922. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Automobile licenses, 1918-1921. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bail bonds, forfeiture of, 1918. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Bank examinier, Chief, 1918-1921. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Battleship Virginia, Daughters of, 1919. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Bee keepers, 1922. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Bills paid and payable, 1917-1918. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Bills paid and payable, 1919. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Bills paid and payable, 1920-1922. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Bills paid and payable, Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Company, 1918-1919. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Bills paid and payable, Post Office box rental, 1918-1921. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Blind, Blindness Prevention Bill, 1918. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Blind, Commission to study conditions of blind in Virginia, 1920. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Biography, 1919. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Blue Ridge Sanitorium, 1920-1921. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Blue Sky Law, 1918-1919. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Boats, 1918. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bonds, 1918-1921. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Book agents, 1920. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Boxing laws, 1920-1921. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1918-1921. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Bureau of vocations for women, 1919-1922. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Cancer, American Society for the control of cancer, 1921. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Canvassers, State Board of, 1918. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Capitol building, Flood lights, 1919. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Capitol building, Orkin the ratman, 1918. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Capitol building, Ventilating dome, 1918-1919. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Capitol building, Ventilating of halls of Senate, 1919-1920. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Capitol Guide, 1919. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Catawba Sanatorium, 1918-1921. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Census, 1920. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1920-1921. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Charities and Corrections, State Board of, 1918. (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Charities and Corrections, State Board of, 1919. (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Charities and Corrections, State Board of, 1920. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Charities and Corrections, State Board of, 1921-1922. (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Charities and Corrections, State Conference, 1921. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Children's Code Commission, 1921-1922. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Children's Home Society of Virginia, 1918-1922. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Churches, 1918. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Cities, Plat of outlying lands, 1918. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Civil Contingent Fund, 1918-1919. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Clubs and Societies, 1918-1921. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Coal, 1920-1921. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Coal Conference, 1920. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Code of Virginia, 1918-1919. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Cold storage and cold storage laws, 1919. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Colonial Dames, 1919-1920. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Colored YMCA, 1918. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Commissioner of Revenue, 1921. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Commonwealth Attorneys, 1918-1922. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Concealed weapons, 1918. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Confederate Museum, 1919. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Confederate, Home for Needy Confederate Women, 1920. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Constitution Day, 1919-1921. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Consuls, 1918-1921. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Contingent expenses, nd. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Corpus Christi (Tx) Hurricane Relief, 1919. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Cotton, 1919 February-April. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Cotton, 1919 May. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Cotton, 1919 July-1920 May. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cotton Conference, 1921. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Court appeals, 1918. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Covington Industrial School and Farm for Homeless Boys, 1918-1919. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Credit Law, 1919. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Crop improvement, Associations, 1921. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Crop Pest Commission, 1918-1921. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Dairy and Food Division, 1917-1919. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Dairy and Food Division, 1920 January. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Dairy and Food Division, 1920 February-November. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Dairy and Food Division, 1922. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Davis House (Washington Building aka Old State Office Building), 1916. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Davis House (Washington Building aka Old State Office Building), 1917 January-March. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Davis House (Washington Building aka Old State Office Building), 1917 April-May. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Davis House (Washington Building aka Old State Office Building), 1917 June-December. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Davis House (Washington Building aka Old State Office Building), 1918. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Davis, Jefferson, Statue in Vicksburg (Miss.), 1921. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Deaf and Blind Virginia School (Staunton, Va.), 1918. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Deaf and Blind Virginia School (Staunton, Va.), 1919 January-August. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Deaf and Blind Virginia School (Staunton, Va.), 1919 September-December. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Deaf and Blind Virginia School (Staunton, Va.), 1920. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Deaf and Blind Virginia School (Staunton, Va.), 1921-1922. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Death penalty, Abolishment of, 1918. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Deeds, Commissioner of, 1915-1922. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Delegates to Conventions Index Cards (alphabetical by cities and counties). (Box 75)
  - Democratic National Congress, 1919. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Dental Examiners, Recommendations for Board, 1918-1919. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Dental Examiners, Recommendations for Board, 1920-1921. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - "Destroyers", List of Virginians, 1919. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Detectives, 1919-1921. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Devany, Judge Walter L., 1919. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Dictograph, 1919. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Directories, 1918. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Disarmament Conference, Appointment of a woman, 1921. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Diseases, Commission on preventable, 1919. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - DC Workhouse Farm (Occoquan, Va.), 1918. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Dog laws, 1918-1919. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Drainage National Congress, 1918-1920. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Drainage National Congress, 1921. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Election laws, 1918-1919. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Election laws, 1920-1921. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Elections to fill vacancies, 1918-1921. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Electors, State Board of, 1921. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Elks, Order of, 1919. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Embalming, State Board of, 1918-1921. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Epileptics and Feeble minded, State Colony for, 1918-1921. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Escheator, Appointment, 1918-1920. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Examiner of Records, Appointments, 1918 February-April 19. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Examiner of Records, Appointments, 1918 April 20-27. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Examiner of Records, Appointments, 1918 May-November. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Examiner of Records, Appointments, 1919. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Examiner of Records, Appointments, 1920 January-February. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Examiner of Records, Appointments, 1920 April-September. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Examiner of Records, Appointments, 1921. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Eugenics, International Congress of, 1921. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Ezekiel, Sir Moses, Funeral, 1918. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Fair Price Commission, 1919-1920. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Farm Demonstration Advisory Council, 1918-1919. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Farm labor, 1918 February-April. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Farm labor, 1918 May. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Farm labor, 1918 June-December. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Farmers National Congress, 1918-1919. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Farmers National Congress, 1920-1921. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Farmers, Federate Farm Bureau of Virginia, 1920-1921. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Farmers, Federal Farm Loan Act, 1918-1921. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Farmers, Farm Women's National Congress, 1920. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Fathers Day, 1920-1922. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Federal Buildings and Grounds, Control of, 1918. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Fertilizers, 1918-1920. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Final Address of Governor Westmoreland Davis, 1922. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Fire prevention, 1918. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Fire prevention, 1919-1921. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Fiscal Year, Uniform, 1918. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Flags, Wm. H. Hortsmann Co., 1919-1921. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Flags, M.C. Lilley & Co., 1918. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Flags, Presentation of to State, 1919-1921. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Flags, 116th Infantry, 1918-1919. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Flags, 117th Infantry, 1918. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Flags, Miscellaneous, 1918-1921. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Flax and Linen Industry, 1920. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Florence Crittenton League of Virginia, 1918. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Flower, State, 1918-1919. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Food conservation, 1918-1919. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Ford, Henry and son, 1918-1919. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - National Reserve in Virginia, 1918-1921. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Forest, Natural Bridge National Forest, 1918. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Forest, Forest warden, 1918-1919. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Forest, Forest warden, 1920. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Forest, Forest warden, 1921 February-August. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Forest, Forest warden, 1921 September-December. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Forester, State, 1918-1921. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Forestry, American Forestry Association, 1918-1920. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Forestry, Southern Forestry Congress, 1919-1922. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - France, 1919-1920. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Freight rates, 1919. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, 1916-1918 March. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, 1918 April-June. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, 1918 July-December. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, 1919. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, 1920. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, 1921-1922. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, H.R. 213, 1921. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - General Assembly, Messages of Governor to, 1918. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - General Assembly, Messages of Governor to, 1919. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - General Assembly, Messages of Governor to, 1920. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly, Messages of Governor to, Requests for copies, 1920. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - General Assembly, Messages of Governor to, Pardon report, 1920-1922. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly, Resignations from, 1921. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Geological Commission, 1918-1922. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Gettysburg National Park, Virginia Memorial, 1919. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Conference, 1918-1919. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Conference, 1920-1921. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Inagural Address, 1918-1921. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Mansion and Office, 1914-1918. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Governor's and Mayor's Conference, 1919. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Governor's Receptions, 1918-1922. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Southern, 1918-1922. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Staff, 1918 March-June. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Staff, 1918 July-December. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Staff, 1919. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Staff, 1920. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Staff, 1921. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Grain Corporations of U.S., 1919. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Grain Elevators on Atlantic Seaboard, 1919. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Greek Prime Minister, 1921. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Guns, 1919. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Hall of Fame, 1919. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Harding, Warren G., 1921. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Hampton (Va.), 1918-1922. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Health appropriations, 1918. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Health, Public Health Service, 1919-1921. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Health, State Board of, 1918-1919. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Health, State Board of, 1920-1921. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Highway Commission, State, 1917-1918. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Highway Commission, State, 1919-1920. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Highway Commission, State, 1921-1922. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Holidays, 1918. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Home Demonstration, 1918. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Homeopathy, American Institute of, 1919. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Hopewell (Va.), 1918. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Hospitals, American Hospital Association Annual Convention, 1918-1919. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Hospitals, Central State Hospital (Petersburg, Va.), 1917-1922. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Hospitals, Commissioner of State Hospitals, 1919-1920. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Hospitals, Eastern State Hospital (Williamsburg, Va.), 1918-1921. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Hospitals, General correspondence and complaints, 1919-1922. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Hospitals, Hospital Farms reports on, 1918-1919. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Hospitals, National Hospital Day, 1921. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Hospitals, Southwestern State Hospital (Marion, Va.), 1918-1921. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Hospitals, Western State Hospital (Staunton, Va.), 1918-1921. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Illinois Centennial Commission, 1918. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Immigration laws, 1918-1921. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Indians, 1918-1921. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Commission on Virginia, 1918-1921. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Influenza, 1918-1919. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Insane, 1918-1919. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Inquiries, 1920. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Insurance, Conditions in Virginia, 1918-1920. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Insurance, Office of the Bureau of Insurance, 1918-1921. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - International Bible Students arrest, 1919 February. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - International Bible Students arrest, 1919 March-August. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Interpreters, 1918. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Inventors, National Institute of, 1918. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Invitations by Governor, 1918-1921. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Irish, 1919-1921. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Italy, 1919-1921. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Jackson, Stonewall, Memorial unveiling, 1919. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Jamestown Island, 1918-1921. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Judges, Appointments, general, 1919-1921. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Judges, Commissions, 1918-1921. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Judges, Corporation Court of Danville(Va.), Petitions, 1919. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Judges, Corporation Court of Danville(Va.), 1919 March-June. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Judges, Corporation Court of Danville(Va.), 1920 September-November 13. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Judges, Corporation Court of Danville(Va.), 1920 November 15-24. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Judges, Designations, 1918-1919. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Judges, Designations, 1921 May-June. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Judges, Designations, 1921 August-September. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Judges, Designations, 1921 October-1922 January. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Judges, Designations, Index Cards. (Box 75)
  - Judges, Supreme Court of Appeals of Virginia, 1919-1922. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Judges, Court of Law and Chancery (Roanoke, Va.), 1919-1921. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Justice and Law Enforcement, Department, 1921. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Justice of the Peace, 1918-1921. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Kindergarten, 1919-1920. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Korea, 1918. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Labor Commissioner, 1918-1919. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Labor Commissioner, 1920-1922. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Labor Commissioner, State, Endorsements of C.G. Kizer, 1917-1918. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Labor, Child Labor Laws, 1918-1919. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Labor, Compulsory Labor Law, 1918. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Labor, Inspectors, State, 1918-1919. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Labor, US Department of Labor, Secretary of Labor, 1917-1919 March. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Labor, US Department of Labor, Secretary of Labor, 1919 April-1920. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Lafayette, Marquis de, Celebrations, 1919. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Land grants, 1918-1919. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Land grants, 1920-1922. (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Land Office, Register of, 1918-1919. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Land Office, Register of, 1920-1922. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Laurel Industrial School (Henrico Co., Va.), 1918-1920 June 11. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Laurel Industrial School (Henrico Co., Va.), 1920 June 11-December 17. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - League of Nations Day, 1920. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Camp Lee (Prince George Co., Va.), 1918-1921. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Lee, Robert E., Memorial, 1919-1920. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Legislation, future, 1918-1921. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Merriweather Lewis Memorial Board, 1918. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Lime Grinding Board, State Convict, 1918 January-June. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Lime Grinding Board, State Convict, 1918 July-December. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Lime Grinding Board, State Convict, 1919. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Lime Grinding Plant, State Convict, 1916-1922. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Lime bins, 1918-1921. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Lists, 1920. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Lynching, 1918-1922. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Manassas Battlefield, 1921. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Manassas Industrial School for Colored Youth, 1918. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Maps, 1918-1920. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Markets, Division of, 1919-1922. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Marriage among feebleminded, etc., 1918. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Maryland Colored Farmers Convention & Exhibition (Salisbury, Md.), 1918. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Mattaponi Indians, 1918. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Matthew Fontaine Maury Association, 1919-1922. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Mayors, List of, 1919. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Medical College of Virginia, 1918-1921. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Medical College of Virginia, Bulletin, 1920. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Medical Examiners, State Board of, 1918-1920. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Memorial Hospital (Richmond, Va.), 1920. (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Methodist Reconstruction Work, 1919. (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Military supplies, Catalogs, 1918. (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Military, Universal training, 1919. (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Militia, 1919-1920. (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Millers, Law of, 1918. (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Mineral lands, 1918-1919. (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Mineral Resources of Virginia (book), 1918. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Mineral Resources of Virginia (book), 1919. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Mineral Resources of Virginia (book), 1920-1922. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Mining, American Mining Congress, 1920-1921. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Monticello (Charlottesville, Va.), 1920-1922. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Mother's Day, 1920-1921. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Motor Vehicle, Law of Virginia, 1918. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Moving Pictures, 1918-1921. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Mount Vernon (Fairfax Co., Va.), 1918-1921. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Multigraph, 1918. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Museum, Custodian of, 1918-1920. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - National Conference of Social Work, 1919-1920. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - National Co-Operative Re-Adjustment Association, 1919. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - National Inland Waterways Association, 1919. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - National Municipal League, 1918-1920. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - National Resources Association, 1918. (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - National Week of Song, 1918. (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Negro Education, Conference on, 1920-1921. (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Newport News City Farm, 1918-1921. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Newport News Jail, 1919. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper interviews, 1918-1919. (Box 25, Folder 3)